# HANIFAH CITRA MARVYNA

+6282231161003 | hanifahcitram123@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/hanifahcitramarvyna/

Surabaya, Indonesia

I'm a bachelor degree of Information System Studies from Nahdlatul Ulama Surabaya University GPA (3.86). Proven good at communication skill and problem solving skills through organizational experiences. Experienced in technical skills as a full-stack web developer intern and also a web tester. Had a strong willingness to learn more especially in IT field.

### **Work Experiences**

Freelancer - Remote Feb 2023 - Present

Quality Assurance

- · Created 200+ test case
- · Performed manually testing on PTOS-M Pelindo, MA Abadiyah Website
- Created QA Evidence Scenario Report
- Created QA Assessment Report

#### PT. Andromedia Indonesia - Surabaya

Feb 2022 - Jul 2022

Full Stack Developer Intern

- · Develop and modified 4 different companies software systems project using React.js and Node.js stack
- Database implementation using PostgreSQL and MySQL
- · Analyzed data usage and work process a WordPress site using Lighthouse

## Indosat Ooredoo Innovation Digital Excellence Academy

Nov 2021 - Jan 2022

(IDEA) - Surabaya

Product Management Intern

- · Develop an idea to releasing a new product i-Library
- · Performing innovation stages (CV, PV, MV)
- · Create a low fidelity prototype i-Library apps using Figma

#### **Education Level**

#### Nahdlatul Ulama Surabaya University - Surabaya

Sep 2019 - May 2023

Bachelor Degree in Information Systems, 3.86/4.00

- · Appointed as a Vice Lead of UKM Cyber Nahdlatul Ulama Surabaya University
- Won 1st Place in My Holiday Program Nahdlatul Ulama Surabaya University 2020 at Article Category
- Won 1st Place in Souvenir Design Competition 2021 by LPPM Nahdlatul Ulama Surabaya University
- Won 1st Place in ISTIC 2021 by Information System Study Program Nahdlatul Ulama Surabaya University at Programming Category
- Won 3rd Place in ISTIC 2021 by Information System Study Program Nahdlatul Ulama Surabaya University at Software Development Category

## SMA Hang Tuah 4 Surabaya - Surabaya

Jun 2015 - May 2018

High School Diploma in Natural Science

### Organisational Experience

#### **UKM Cyber Nahdlatul Ulama University**

Aug 2021 - Dec 2021

Vice Lead

· Assisting the Lead in organizing the work program of the committee

### Information Systems Major Orientation (Formoster) - Surabaya

Dec 2020 - Jan 2021

**Event Division** 

- Responsible for planning, organizing, managing Formoster events
- Selected to be MC to guide 40+ participants during Formoster

### Faculty of Engineering Student Orientation

Sep 2020 - Oct 2020

Mentor

- Mentoring 40+ new college student to know more about engineering faculty of Nahdlatul Ulama Surabaya University
- Supervise and guide 40+ new college students activities

#### Surabaya Hacker Link - Surabaya

Jan 2020 - Present

• Archiving organization documents, organization structure, preparing and collating reports and also letters

### Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Language: Indonesia, English
- Hard Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.JS, MySQL, API, Git Versioning
- Tools: Microsoft Office, VsCode, Github, Figma, Katalon, Postman, Trello, Jira